Guide to the Kathleen George Papers, 1962-2014 CTC.2012.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Kathleen George Papers
1962-2014
ULS Archives & Special Collections
George, Kathleen
CTC.2012.02
36 Linear Feet (80 document boxes)
Kathleen George is a professor in the Theatre Arts Department at the University of Pittsburgh and an accomplished author. This collection contains drafts of her books and short stories, along with the research and promotional materials related to these works. Materials representing her 30 plus years of teaching can also be found in the collection.
Acquisition Information
Gifts donated by Kathleen George in 2012-2014.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection documents Kathleen George's lifelong passion for teaching and creative writing. The papers include materials relating to the creation and publishing of all of her creative works, along with files related to her academic career, primarily at the University of Pittsburgh.
Related to her academic career, the collection contains materials on many of the courses that she taught. There is also documentation for the Pitt theatre productions that she directed and her work with the Semester at Sea program.
The largest group of materials are related to Dr. George's literary works. There are many different varieties of output for her writing – academic articles, theatre reviews, book reviews, short fiction, academic and instructional text books, novels, etc. All of Dr. George's unpublished works are also contained in the collection and are available for use.
Arrangement
The papers are organized into four series.
Series I. Academic Career, 1978-2011
Series II. Correspondence and Other Materials, 1964-2009
Series III. Writing Career, 1961-2014
Series IV. Oversized Materials, 1979-2012
Related Material
Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival Records, 1980-1995, CTC.1995.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
University of Pittsburgh Theatre Arts Department Records, 1960-1986, CTC.1974.02, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Previous Citation
Kathleen George Papers, 1962-2014, CTC.2012.02, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh.
Biography
Kathleen George was born in Johnstown, Pennsylvania, in 1943. She attended college at the University of Pittsburgh's Johnstown campus for several years before transferring to Pitt's main campus in 1963. She received her bachelor of arts in English with an emphasis on creative writing in 1964, and her Master's degree in Theatre Arts in 1966. Afterwards, she took an assistant professor position at Carlow College (1968-1976). In 1975, she completed her PhD in Theatre from Pitt and the next year became an associate professor there. Throughout the 1980s and 90s she directed many productions for the University of Pittsburgh Repertory Theatre and the Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival. Also, during this time she published two academic works, her dissertation Rhythm in Drama and Playwriting: the First Workshop.
Kathleen had been writing since she was a teenager and in 1988, she completed a second Masters of Fine Arts degree in creative writing. Her first of many published short stories was Country Tale in the journal Valhalla, in the fall of 1980. Throughout the eighties and nineties, she continued to have her short fiction published in a variety of journals. This culminated in the 1999 publication of a collection of these short stories, The Man in the Buick. Since then, Kathleen has found great success with a series of novels featuring Pittsburgh Police detective Richard Christie. The Odds, the fourth book in the series, was nominated for an Edgar award for best novel of 2009 by the Mystery Writers of America.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions other than Box 20, Folders 5-11 which will be closed until 2040.
Manuscripts for publication; Personal papers; Women authors, American -- 20th century; Detective and mystery stories, American -- Women authors; Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616 -- Stage history -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Performing arts -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; College theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Faculty papers; George, Kathleen; Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival (Pittsburgh, Pa.); University of Pittsburgh. Department of Theatre Arts
- Academic Career, 1978-2011; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series contains materials related to Kathleen George's academic career. While the vast majority of the files are centered around her faculty position here at the University of Pittsburgh, there are a few files that relate to her time as an assistant professor at Carlow College. The series is divided into four subseries - Directing, Semester at Sea, Student Plays, and Teaching and Advising.
  - Directing, 1978-1984; 1.
    Dr. George has directed over a dozen productions for the University of Pittsburgh Repertory Theatre. This includes several productions for the Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival. Materials incorporated into each production's section include scripts, research files, audition forms, rehearsal information, slides, set designs, reviews, etc. The sections are arranged in chronological order.
    - The Rehearsal, 1977
      University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of The Rehearsal ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre March 10-26, 1977.
      - Production information, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Country Wife, 1978
      University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of The Country Wife ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre March 3-18, 1978.
      - Production information, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Report on Restoration Comedy by Dr. Wandalie Henshaw and Kathy George (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Slides (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Much Ado About Nothing, 1978-1979
      University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of Much Ado About Nothing ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre November 1-17, 1978. It was a very popular production and was revived the next season as well as making it to the semi-finals of the American College Theatre Festival competition.
      - American College Theatre Festival - Audio of critique after performance in the semi-finals, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Production information, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
      - Costume plots (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Major Barbara, 1979
      University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of Major Barbara ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre November 1-17, 1979.
      - Music Hall sheet music (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Production information, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Canterbury Tales, 1980
      This production of Canterbury Tales was performed at the Studio Theatre in the Cathedral of Learning, September 18-27, 1980. The City Theatre Company production also toured the Pittsburgh area in the Summer of 1980.
      - Music (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Production information, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Script (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Set design, April 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Story Theatre, 1980
      Story Theatre toured Pittsburgh area schools in the fall of 1980. It was a production of the City Theatre Company.
      - Production information, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Set design, October 1, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Company, 1980-1981
      University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of Company ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre March 5-21, 1981.
      - Production information, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Scripts with annotations (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Set design (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Winter's Tale, 1981
      The Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival production of The Winter's Tale ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre July 9 - 25, 1981.
      - Newspaper clippings, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Production information, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Set design, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - She Stoops to Conquer, 1981
      University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of Much Ado About Nothing ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre November 5-21, 1981.
      - Correspondence, September 3, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Production information, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Script (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Hamlet, 1982
      The Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival production of Hamlet ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre June 17 - July 3, 1982.
      - Feedback, June 24, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Production information, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Set design, April 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Lysistrata, 1982
      University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of The Glass Menagerie ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre November 4-20, 1982.
      - Newspaper clippings, November 1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Production information, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Rehearsal materials, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Script (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Slides (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - The Dining Room, April 1984
      The Dining Room was presented by the S.S. Universe Theatre at Sea on April 14-15, 1984. This production was staged while Kathleen George was a part of the Semester at Sea program.
      - Production information, April 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - A Flea in Her Ear, 1984
      University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of A Flea in Her Ear ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre November 1-17, 1984.
      - Costume research (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Music, October 1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Production information, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Scripts with annotations (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Set design (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - The Glass Menagerie, 1985-1986
      University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of The Glass Menagerie ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre January 30 - February 15, 1986.
      - Production information, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Prompt book and script, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Rehearsal - Schedule and notes, December 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Research (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Set design (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - King Lear, 1986
      The Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival production of King Lear ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre July 25 - August 17, 1986.
      - Newspaper clippings, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Production information, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
      - Research (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Script with annotations (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Set design, July 1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Slides (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Our Town, 1998-1999
      University of Pittsburgh Theatre's production of Our Town ran at the Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre March 31 - April 18, 1999.
      - Casting, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Costumes (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Music, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Production information, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Performances for high school students, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Publicity and dramaturgy, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Rehearsal and performance reports, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Reviews, April 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Script with annotations (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Set design, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Her First American, 1997-2006
      University of Pittsburgh Repertory Theatre's production of Her First American ran at the Studio Theatre in the Cathedral of Learning, April 13 - 17, 2005. The play was also adapted by Kathleen George from the novel by Lore Segal.
      - Correspondence - Lore Segal, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Dramatic rights and early script, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Faculty of Arts and Sciences grants committee application, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts stipend and contact list, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Production and rehearsal information, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5-7)
      - Program and flyers, April 2005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Script, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Script - Assistant director's copy, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Script - Revised (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
      - Script - Revised, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Script - With Lore Segal notes, January 2006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Semester at Sea, 1982-1995; 2.
    Kathleen George served as Associate Professor for the Semester at Sea study abroad program in the spring of 1984. In the Fall of 1987, she was the Academic Dean of the program. This subseries contains materials related to the curriculum during these semesters, memos, reports, and information on some of the cities that were visiting during the voyages. Also included in the subseries is one folder of materials from the Spring semester of 1995, where she was an Associate Professor for the Pitt in London program.
    - Advisory committee, 1986-1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Appointment letter, August 1, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Captain's meetings - Agendas, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - China and Japan - Articles and notes (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Course descriptions - Fall, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Core course - Fall, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Core course - Speech (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Core course - Spring, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Core course - Workshops and surveys, 1983-1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Core course memos- Fall, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Field program, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Information file - Spring, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Information file - Spring, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Library - Fall, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - London program - Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Memos, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Port information - Brochures and fact sheets (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Practice letters, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Report, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Report of the Academic Dean, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Student Plays, 1986-2008; 3.
    Kathleen George began teaching playwriting courses at the University of Pittsburgh in the mid-1980s. This series collects all the student written plays from these courses that were staged in some form. Some of these plays were a part of the New Play Practicum and Lunchtime Theatre series of productions. In most instances, only the script is present. Also included are different drafts of the play, copies of the script with annotations by Kathleen, rehearsal information, etc. The files are arranged alphabetically by the author.
    - Bailey, Cathleen - Loving, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Carr, Daniel - Love, Seducing the Audience, The Best Seat in the House, Untitled, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Carney, Erin - Wonder, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Chiplman, Jay Scott - You Hear That? (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Damp, Michael J. - Soap etc., November 26, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Gabriel - Breakfast at Jake's, Hope, Mad Love with Jill, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Denman, Stan - The Etiquette of Mourning, March 22, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Donohue, Kate - Accomplices (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Flynn, Erin - Double Entendree (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Focareta, Cathy - Where's Mom? (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Focareta, Dean - Real Life Bullshit (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Fox, Pete - The Judgment (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Gallagher, Brendan - Eight Times (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Hansen, Joshua - What's He Building in There? (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Hiller, Monica - Patients (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Honard, Justin - Oh, Roy and Jasper; Jasper and Roy, Splattered Gin and Broken Glass, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Hunter, Jenna - Becoming Janis (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Jenkins, Maureen - Oak Trees, November 10, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, Miki - The Man and Woman C (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Jumbelic, Josh - Simple Game of Catch, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kerr, Brendan - Forgetting Yourself, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Krug, Breon W. - Just Friends (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Landis, Gary - Death in Gb, January 9, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Ledford, Lindsay - Healthy Variety, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Lee, Insoo - Wandering (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Lehner, Frank - Four for Cheese, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Mesaris, Darcey - Three by Vonnegut, January 2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Pollock, Beverly King - It's Business, By the Book, No Magic Hero, Looking for "Magic", 1991-2007 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Potocki, Chris - Another AIDS Play (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Rosenstein, Anna - Constructing Margaret or Down the Path of Womanhood with Judy Blume (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Ruefle, Bob - Sex Drive (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Schwartz, Michael - Istanbul (Not Constantinople), Hangin' Up My Heart (Box 12, Folder 5-7)
    - Sclove, Sarabeth - An Unmentionable Mistake, December 5, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Scott, Jenn - Chameleon (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Shames, Jade - Flush (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Sickles, Scott C. - The Simple Act of Walking Away, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
    - Staf, Mark - Slayed Them (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Tamler, Cory - Not Eureka, The Sheep Game (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Tindall, A.J. - And a Happy New Year (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Trobin, Pat - Anniversary Tango (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Vogel, Scott - We Need F.D.R., 1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Teaching and Advising, 1978-2012; 4.
    This subseries contains materials related to Kathleen George various responsibilities as part of the faculty of the Theatre Arts Department at the University of Pittsburgh. There are files dealing with courses taught, dissertation committees, student playwriting and productions, teaching evaluations, department memos, yearly reports, etc. There are also several items from here time teaching at Carlow College.
    - Acting course, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - American Biographical Institute, 1992-1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Audition sheets - Blank (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Bellet College of Arts and Sciences Teaching Excellence Award - Dossier materials, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Bellet College of Arts and Sciences Teaching Excellence Award - Stage two dossier, March 2002 (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
    - BEST North America Faculty Expertise Database, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Carlow College materials - Lecture (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Carlow College materials - Productions (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Carlow University - Writing programs, 1992, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Chatham University low residency MFA in creative writing program, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Commonly used scenes for introduction to acting course (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Contemporary American Drama course, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Contemporary Authors entry, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Contemporary Theatre (England) course, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Dissertation committee member - Brittany Conkle, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Dissertation committee member - Cory Tamler, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Dissertation committee member - J.A. Ball (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Dissertation committee member - Meredith Conti, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Dissertation committee member - Siyuan Liu, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Exchange Colloquium with Ohio State University, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Fiction workshop, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - First Experiences in Research - College of Arts and Sciences student poster session, April 19, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Graduate student handbook, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Graduate studies, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Grant proposal to produce Sarabeth Sclove's Quality of Life - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Improvisation course - Related materials, 1986-2009 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
    - Introduction to Dramatic Art course, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Introduction to Performance course (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Introduction to Shakespeare course, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Introduction to Theatre course (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Introduction to Theatre Arts course, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Letters in support of George's tenure, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Lunchtime Theatre (Playwright's lab series), 1991-1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Lunchtime Theatre (Playwright's lab series) - Clippings, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Master of Fine Arts in Writing programs - Information gathering, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - New Play Festival, 2006, 2011-2012 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - New Play Practicum course, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - New Play Practicum - Flyers (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - New Play Practicum - Productions, 2008-2012 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Past students - Clippings and correspondence, 1987-2011 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Playwriting courses, 1998-2006 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Playwriting courses - Proposals, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Promotion materials, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
    - Promotion materials (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - Script analysis course, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Seminar in Dramatic Rhythm, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Seminar in Narrative and Drama, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Shakespeare Week at Penn State University Fayette campus, January 1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Study abroad in London - Faxes, November 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Summer productions for freshman - Ed! and In Mad Love with Jill, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Teaching - Acknowledgements, 1998-2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Teaching evaluations, 1989-1994 (Box 18, Folder 10-13)
    - Teaching evaluations, 1994-2008 (Box 19, Folder 1-12)
    - Teaching evaluations, 2008-2012 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
    - Teaching - Peer review, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Theatre Arts Department - Correspondence and memos, 1978-2011 (Box 20, Folder 5-11)
      Access Restrictions
      Some of the materials in these folders are restricted. Access to these materials will be permitted in 2040.
    - Theatre Arts Department - Flyers and handouts (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Theatre criticism course, 1994-2001 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Theatre study in London proposal, April 9, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Western Pennsylvania Writing Project - Workshop evaluations, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Who's Who publications, 1996-2001 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Woman's Association of the University of Pittsburgh at Johnstown, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Workshops for the Guild for the Blind, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Yearly reports, 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 19-21)
    - Yearly reports, 1994-2008 (Box 21, Folder 1-12)
    - Yearly reports, 2008-2012 (Box 22, Folder 1-4)
- Correspondence and Other Materials, 1964-2009; II.
  Included in this series is a small amount of correspondence and a few other files that are not directly related to Kathleen George's academic or writing work. Within the correspondence files are letters from colleagues such as Bert O. States and Montgomery Culver. Also included are reader's reports for the University of Pittsburgh Press, copies of her curriculum vitae from different points of her career, and information files on some of her mentors.
  - Academic records, 1964-1985 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - ***Autobiographical notes
  - Curriculum vitae, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Montgomery Culver, 1987-2009 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Sandra A. Tausend, 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and writings - Becky R. Edgerton, 1988-2000 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence and writings - Bert O. States, 1974-1999 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Weingel-Fidel Literary Agency, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Diplomas and commencement program, 1964,1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Marian Varner - Information file, 1991-2003 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - New Works Festival, 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Pitt Players, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 16)